<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home</title>
    <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.jacobsargent.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Closed on Sundays</title>
      <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/posts/cfa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jacobsargent.com/posts/cfa/</guid>
      <description>Closed on Sundays A Love Letter to Chick-Fil-A When you think about Chick-Fil-A, what comes to mind?
For some, it&amp;rsquo;s service, hospitality, and a really good, if not kind of expensive chicken sandwich.
For others, it&amp;rsquo;s intolerance, arcane beliefs, and a distortion of Christianity.
Of course, like any business, CFA is made up of thousands of employees and sub-companies, so it&amp;rsquo;s not like there&amp;rsquo;s a consensus on any one issue. But unlike other companies, CFA is privately-held and centered around the leadership of their executive committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to the Blog</title>
      <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/posts/blog-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jacobsargent.com/posts/blog-intro/</guid>
      <description>Intro to the Blog
I have never been one to make public statements. As far as publically available information and opinions go, people accept the ones they agree with and distance themselves from difference.
My purpose in creating this blog is to provide people who already know me with a resevoir of my thoughts, so that they might see how someone they thought believed in something, really believed in something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Jacob</title>
      <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jacobsargent.com/about/</guid>
      <description>The Basics Education: Economics Major at Clemson University (4.0/4.0)
Proficiencies:
 Computer Science - scripting, back-end web development, demystifying tech Political Science - policy analysis, political research German Language &amp;amp; Culture - advanced French Language - intermediate  Interests:
 Education Policy Reform Trivia Start-ups Pokemon  In a paragraph I try to make peoples&amp;rsquo; days easier. Whether that&amp;rsquo;s automating the most frustrating part of their workday or cracking bad jokes every so often.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jacobsargent.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me on everything, @jvsarge.
Email is the best way to reach me: jacobvsargent@gmail.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First snippet</title>
      <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/snippets/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jacobsargent.com/snippets/first/</guid>
      <description>This content is in snippets/first/index.md
pwd </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jacobsargent.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Bet On It Bet On It is another project by me and Nick Deas (@nickdeas). The website and app are currently in development, but this is where it will be once it&amp;rsquo;s done.
https://betonit.biz
Clemson Nights Clemson Nights is a project I&amp;rsquo;m working on with my sister, Emma. We are working with Clemson&amp;rsquo;s local restaurants and bars to highlight nightly specials on food &amp;amp; drink. The website is almost finished, and we will officially launch once it is safe to eat out again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second snippet</title>
      <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/snippets/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jacobsargent.com/snippets/second/</guid>
      <description>This content is in snippets/second/index.md
ls -la </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>