<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on Home</title>
    <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/series/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.jacobsargent.com/series/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my World</title>
      <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/posts/wtmw/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jacobsargent.com/posts/wtmw/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Real World or, &amp;ldquo;your way of doing things sucks&amp;rdquo; Family beach trip. 15 people. Pizza night. Got it?
We ordered Papa John&amp;rsquo;s at about 6:30 on a Tuesday. Soon after, storms took the power of our whole house, neighborhood, and apparently every Papa John&amp;rsquo;s within a 10-mile radius. Obviously there would be some sort of delay.
8:30: no word.
So we called to check in, and they said that a Doordash deliveryman had left the restaurant about 35 minutes prior with our order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Closed on Sundays</title>
      <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/posts/cfa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jacobsargent.com/posts/cfa/</guid>
      <description>Closed on Sundays A Love Letter to Chick-Fil-A When you think about Chick-Fil-A, what comes to mind?
For some, it&amp;rsquo;s service, hospitality, and a really good, if not kind of expensive chicken sandwich.
For others, it&amp;rsquo;s intolerance, arcane beliefs, and a distortion of Christianity.
Of course, like any business, CFA is made up of thousands of employees and sub-companies, so it&amp;rsquo;s not like there&amp;rsquo;s a consensus on any one issue. But unlike other companies, CFA is privately-held and centered around the leadership of their executive committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intro to the Blog</title>
      <link>http://www.jacobsargent.com/posts/blog-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jacobsargent.com/posts/blog-intro/</guid>
      <description>Intro to the Blog
I have never been one to make public statements. As far as publically available information and opinions go, people accept the ones they agree with and distance themselves from difference.
My purpose in creating this blog is to provide people who already know me with a resevoir of my thoughts, so that they might see how someone they thought believed in something, really believed in something else.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>